Guide to the Physics Department records, 1930-2005 RG0077
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office records, 1977-1990; Series 3; 7.5 Linear feet
  - Chakrabatry, Subrata, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chao, Shao-Hua, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chen, Chia-Rong, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Christou, Carol, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cohen, Joseph, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Delic, George, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Elminyawi, Imam M., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Furnstahl, Richard J., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Garcilazo, Humberto, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Girija, V., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Hanna, Kamal M., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Harindranath, Avaroth, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Iqbal, M.J., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Ji, Cheung-Ryong, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Kalbermann, Geramn, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Klein, James J., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Koruoglu, Zeki, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Kwok-Keun Liu, Quincy, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Li, Ming, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Linsay, James, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Machleidt, Ruprecht, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Maize, Mohamed Anis, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Department of Energy Contract: Year 5, 02/1983-01/1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Department of Energy Contract: Year 4, 02/1982-01/1983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Department of Energy Contract: Year 3, 02/1981-01/1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Department of Energy Contract: Years 1 and 2, 02/1979-01/1981 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Lewis, David, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Matthew, Edward, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Matthew, Scott, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Najemeddine, Mohamed, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Nicholas, Nancy Jo, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Pittas, Phillip, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Woloschek, John, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Younes, Walid, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Kendall, Kenneth, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Ian, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Carress, Rebecca, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Dragic, Sinisa, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Kuruoglu, Zeki, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Deans Council, 10/1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Deans Council, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - CSAS Dean Council, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - CSAS Dean Council, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - CSAS Honor Program Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Requests for Wage Account Action, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Action Forms: Personnel and Budget, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Gregory Anderson, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Teaching, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Teaching, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Teaching, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Executive Aide: Position Recall, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Council on Academic Computing and Information Services, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bitnet Mail Output, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bitnet Mail Output, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bitnet Messages, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bitnet Messages, 01/1988-07/1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bitnet Messages, 08/1988-04/1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bitnet, 04/1989-10/1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bitnet, 10/1989-05/1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bitnet, 05/1990-10/1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Florida State University: Computing [1/2], 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Florida State University: Computing [2/2], 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - McLeod, Robert J., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Miller, Hank, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mohanty, Ajaya K., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Parmentola, John A., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Poenisch, Volker, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Saha, Bidahn C., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Singham, Mano, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Stoyanov, Aleksandr, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Van Orden, J. Wallace, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Warty, Mardhav, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Wenes, Geert, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Weyrauch, Michael, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Williams, Anthony G., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Wittman, Richard, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Search Application Inquiries: No Action, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Blankleider, Boris, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Carlson, Joseph A. (Physics), 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Chen, Chia-Rong (Physics), 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Van Orden, J. Wallace (Physics), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Weyrauch, Michael (Physics), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Haberzettl, Helmut, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Search: Theory Assistant Professor, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Search: Theory Postdoc., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Postdoc Inquiries: Nuclear Theory, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Ottenstein, Neil A., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Tanabe, Hiroyoshi, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Berhold, Gunther Herbert, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Buchmann, Alfonz J., 07/1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Bicudo, Petro, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Canton, Luciano, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Cao, Zongjian, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Chinn, Clayton R., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Chung, Ping Ling, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Esakndarian, Ali, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Kim, Eun Joo, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Kruppa, Andras T., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Liu, Huan, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Luo, Hong De, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Pourkaviani, Moshen, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Spence, John R., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Yen, Granddon D., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Ghosh, Budhade, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Khan, Ferdous, 05/1989 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Mdlalose, T. E., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Sunyal, Sudip, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Bennhold, Cornelius, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Research Assistant Professor, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Council and Chairs information, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Faculty Surveys: Physics, 03/1987 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - University Policy and Related Matters for Deptartment, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Chairs: General Memoranda To and From, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Matters--Students, 01/1989-01/1990 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence Associated with Chair, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Useful Information: Physics Department, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Information Memos to Chairman, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Teaching, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Office records, 1973-1990; Series 4; 6 Linear feet
  This series includes graduate applicants, speaker invitation letters, conferences/workshops, budget info, summaries of fiscal year, and course syllabi. They range in date from 1973-90.
- Office records, 1980-1995; Series 5; 9 Linear feet
  This series includes correspondence, memos, course materials, budget summaries, staff papers. They range in date from 1980-95.
  - Northern Virginia Campus - Shop Machinery - Details, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Teaching: Summer, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Teaching: Fall, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Teaching: Spring, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Teaching: Summer, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Teaching: Fall, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Teaching: Spring, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University Policy, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chair's Memos - General, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Matters, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Student/Graduate School of Arts and Sciences materials, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chariman's Memos (Special), 09/1987-12/1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences Matters, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Budget Summary Reports, 07/01/1990-06/01/1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Budget Summery Reports and LR 010s, 07/1990-06/1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Misc. Correspondence associated with the Chair, 06/1991-05/1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Information Memos to Chair, 06/1991-05/1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Useful Information, 06/1989-06/1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Personnel Committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate Program Brochure, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences Accreditation Review, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Hobbs Retirement Party, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Master Course Data Forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - SEARCH: Exp Nucl. Physics assistant professor, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Hiroshi Ito: visiting appointment, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Y. Koika - visiting scholar, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Search: Condensed matter, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Papandreou, Zisis PhD (Univ of Regina, Canada), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Misc. correspondence associated with the chair, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Information memos to the chair, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Useful information, 06/1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Academic Program Review (original copy), 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Review Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Departmental Program Review, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Academic/Research Plan, 04/19987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Coordinated Planning/Physics, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Teaching: Summer, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Teaching: Spring, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Teaching: Fall, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Teaching: Spring, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Binder: Chairman's Memos, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Binder: Columbian College of Arts and Sciences Matters, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Binder: Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Matters, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Binder: Departmental - General, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Binder: Departmental - Matters (Confidential), undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Physics Department Evaluation, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Council of Chairs/Information vol. 1, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Council of Chairs/Information vol. 2, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Departmental Budget - BSRs and LR010s, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Departmental Budget Summary Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Budget Summary Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Budget Summary Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Registration Reports, 06/1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Physics/Renovations/Space/Facilities, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Charge of Academic Dishonesty" Forms, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Departmental Planning Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Berman, B., undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Briscoe, W.J. [1/2], undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Briscoe, W.J. [2/2], undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - E. Harper, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - H. Hobbs, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - N. Khatcheressian, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Koike, Yasuro, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - D. Lehman, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - L. Maximon, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Alireza Mokhtari, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - W. Parke, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - J.R. Peverly [1/2], undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - J.R. Peverly [2/2], undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Prats, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - M. Taragin, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - J. Zuchelli, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Council of Chairs vol. 4, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - O. Bergmann, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Physics Faculty, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Budget Summary Reports, 07/01/1989-06/30/1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Info Memos to Chair, 01/1989-05/1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Council of Chairs vol. 3, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Info Memos to Chair, 05/1990-06/1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Misc. Correspondence assoc. with Chair, 01/1989-05/1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Misc. Correspondence assoc. with Chair, 05/1990-06/1991 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - NDL Construction, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - ARP & PDA Search, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Keith Baker, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cole, Phillip Lawrence, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Searches: ENP, CMP, TNP, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dual Degree Program, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Budget Summary Reports, 06/1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fax info/department, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Campus, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sabbatical Leave Forms, 05/1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Program - "Typical Programs", 11/1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Physical Plant Procedures, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Possibilities for lab equipment, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - VARP ads, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - VARP, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Search: Vis. Prof, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Minority Recruitment, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Other students, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Zisis Papandreou - Review Materials, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Zisis Papandreou, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - David Wiesler - Review Materials, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Wiesler [1/3], undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Wiesler [2/3], undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - James P. Connelly Review Materials, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Connelly [1/2], undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Connelly [2/2], undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Connelly, James P. PhD, 05/1989 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Garino, Gerard, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Wiesler [3/3], undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Mark Johnson, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Berman, Barry, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Briscoe, William, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dhuga, Kalvir, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Haberzettl, Helmut, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Harper, Edmond, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Maximon, Lenoard C, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mokhtari, Ali, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Parke, William, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Peverley, Roger, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Prats, Francisco, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Taragin, Morton, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Teaching: Fall, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Teaching: Summer, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Beise, Elizabeth J. PhD, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Feldman, Gerald, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Masson, Grant S., undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Philip L. Cole [1/3], undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Philip L. Cole [2/3], undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Philip L. Cole [3/3], undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Rugari, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Doug Zubanov, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Departmental files, 1935-2000; Series 6; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains articles, announcements, correspondence, reports, invitation, press releases, and brochures. They range in date from 1935 to 2000. The materials concern Washington Conferences on Theoretical Physics, Dr. Niels Bohr, invitation lists, conference planning, Carnegie Institution of Washington, The George Washington University School of Engineering's "Engineering Form", the Physics Department, physics courses, and lecture series.
  - Physics Conferences--Washington Conferences On Theoretical Physics (1935-1947), 1957-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Physics Conferences--Washington Conferences On Theoretical Physics Correspondence, etc., 1935-1947, 03/19/1935-08/26/1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Physics Conferences--Washington Conferences On Theoretical Physics Report, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Physics Conferences--Washington Conferences On Theoretical Physics Report, 1938, 06/27/1938-07/1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Physics Department, 04/1935-05/03/2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Office records (2011.065 accretion), 1967-2005; Series 7; George Washington University. Dept. of Physics; 3 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged by the department.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by Physics Department, 2011 September 28 (2011.064)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains research reports and other material related to the research work of the faculty in the Physics Department. The material dates from 1967-2005.
  - Backgrounds in and shielding of the Photon Tagger and the CLAS, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Selected Activities in Photonuclear Reactions, 1973-1974; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lawerence Livermore Laboratory Photonuclear Program, 1976; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Solar Neutrinos: A Proposed Laboratory Test, 1977; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photonuclear Cross Sections for 180, 1978; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Atlas of Photoneuton Cross Sections obtained with Monoenergetic Photons, 1976; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Indiana University Cyclotron Facility Technical and Scientific Report, 1978; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photonuclear Reactions at the Lawerence Livermore Laboratory, 1978; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photonuclear Reactions at the Lawerence Livermore Laboratory, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photonuclear Measurements on fissionable isotopes using monoenergetic photons, 1976; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Atlas of Photoneuton Cross Sections obtained with Monoenergetic Photons-supplement, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Indiana University Cyclotron Facility Technical and Scientific Report, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Indiana University Cyclotron Facility Technical and Scientific Report, 1981; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Neutron-Capture Resonances in Osmium Isotopes, 1982; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Few Body Problems and Neutron Induced Reactions, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Photonuclear Reactions at the Lawerence Livermore Laboratory, 1984; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Electroexcitation of Low Lying 1-, 3-, 5- states in 180, 1990; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - In vivo whole-boyd nitrogen and Calcium Imaging using Nuclear Rasonance Absorbtion, 1992; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Photofission at CEBAF Energies, 1992; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Isopin Effects in the Photodisintergration of Light Nuclei, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Photonuclear Reactions at Lawerence Livermore National Laboratory, 1982; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Indiana University Cyclotron Facility Scientific and Technical Report, 1982; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bates Linear Accelerator Annual and Scientific Technical Report, 1984; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Observation of Transition Radiation at LLNL Linac opens Possibility for development of pulsed soft x-ray source, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bates Linear Accelerator Annual and Scientific Technical Report, 1985; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Progress at LAMPF, 1987; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Progress at LAMPF, 1988; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bates Linear Accelerator Annual and Scientific Technical Report, 1987-88; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bates Linear Accelerator Annual and Scientific Technical Report, 1989; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bates Linear Accelerator Annual and Scientific Technical Report, 1990; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - A Large Novel Neutron Detector For Basic Nuclear Physics Studies, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - The Origin of Xenon-131 on the moon, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Threshold Photoneutron Cross Section for Mg25 and Isobaric Analogs of Na25, 1970; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Reaction, mechanism and spectroscopic results of the (e, e', d) reaction, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Contributed Papers International Conference on Statistical Properties of Nuclei, 1971; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Total Photoneutron Cross Section for 170, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Coherent Radiation from correlated collisions of positrons with Si*, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Radiation from Channeled Leptons Abstract Submission to 8th international conference on atomic collisions in solids, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Photodisintergration of three-body nuclei, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Coulomb Dissociaton of 180, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - A test of E2 virtual-photon spectra, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Photonuclear Cross Sections of 29Si and 30 Si, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Proceedings of the international conference on nuclear structure, 1982; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Abstract for an Invited Paper for the 8th conference on the application of acceleratos in Researcha and Industry:Channeling Radiation measurements at the Lawerence Livermore National Laboratory, 1984; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - On the temperature and Length Dependence of Channeling Radiation from 54-Mev Electrons in Silicon, 1985; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Abstract:Transition Radiations a coherent soft x-ray source, 1986; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - The 6Li (e, e', d) 4Hegs reaction*, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Transition Radiation as an x-ray source for Lithography, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Pion scattering from 3H and 3He, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Keynote Address at the first international conference on coherent radiation processes in strong fields, 1990; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - A Channeling Radiation as an x-ray source fro Angiography, x-ray lithography, molecular structure determination and elemental analysis, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Angiography using channeling radiation as an x-ray source, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Comparison of Elastic Scattering Cross Sections for Pions for 3H and 3He in the Backward hemisphere, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Channeling Radiation as and x-ray source for angiography, x-ray lithography, molecular structure determination and elemental analysis, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Elastic and Inelastic Scattering from the 3He and 3H in the region of the non-spin-flip Dip, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Back-angle cross sections for pi scattering from 3H and 3He near the ? resonance, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Elastic Scattering of Pions from 3H and 3He in the Backward Hemisphere, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Photonuclear Physics 1986-1988 The George Washington University Abstracts and Lists of Papers, Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Third Topical Meeting on Short Wavelength Coherent Radiatio:Generation and Applications, 1986; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Request for funding support to continue the program of photonuclear reactions at LLL, 1977; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Giant Resonance in Transitional Nuclei:Photoneutron cross sections for osium isotopes, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Photoneutron Cross Section for 4He+, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Photoneutron cross sections of Li6+, 1965; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Cross Sections for the Ground and Excited-State Neutron Groups in the reaction O16(y,n) O15, 1965; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Photoneutron Cross Sections for C12 and Al27+, 1966; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Photoneutron cross sections of Pr141 and I27 from Threshold to 33MeV, 1966; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Threshold Photoneutron Cross Sections for Iron and Bismuth, 1966; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Measurement of the response of a Large NaI (TL) Scintulator to High-Energy Photons, 1959; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Photoneutron Measurements obtained with monochromatic Photons, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Photoneutron cross Sections for Zr90, Zr91, Zr92, Zr94 and y89, 1967; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Threshold Photoneutron Cross Section for Fe56, 1967; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Threshold Photoneutron Cross Section for Be9, 1967; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Energy Levels of Zirconium Isotopes, 1968; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Photoneutron Cross Sections for As75,Ag107, and Cs133, 1969; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Electromagnetic Transition Strengths in Pb206, Pb207, Pb208 from threshold Photoneutron cross-section measurements, 1969; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Effect of Nuclear Polarizationon the Giant Dipole Resonance in Ho165, 1969; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Threshold Photoneutron cross Section for Mg26 and a source of stellar neutrons, 1969; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Gamma-Ray width of the "doorway' state in Pb207 from threshold photoneutron cross section measurements, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 78)